35 millimeter slides
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- 35 millimeter slides, 2.1.5.1
  - Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea], circa 1963; 11 (Box 1590)
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Native man holding a spear], 12
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Close-up of a native man wearing a headdress and holding a spear], 13
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Close-up of a native man wearing a headdress], 14
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Close-up of a native man wearing a headdress], 15
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Close-up of a native man wearing a headdress], 16
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Close-up of a native man with a red painted face], 17
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Native wearing an unusual costume], 18
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Native man wearing a headdress and holding a spear], 19
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Native with a red painted face], 20
  - Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea], circa 1963; 12 (Box 1590)
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Group of natives holding spears], 1
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Some natives holding hand-crafted shields in front of them], 2
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Native wearing a grand headdress], 3
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Group of natives with painted faces, holding spears], 4
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Some native men sitting on the ground wearing headdresses], 5
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Some native men sitting on the ground wearing headdresses], 6
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Some native men sitting on the ground wearing headdresses], 7
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Some native men sitting on the ground wearing headdresses and holding spears], 8
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Some native men sitting on the ground wearing headdresses and holding spears], 9
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Native men wearing grass skirts and holding spears], 10
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Natives hauling a log?], 11
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Some native men sitting on the ground wearing headdresses and holding spears], 12
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Three native women standing together wearing headdresses], 13
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Three native women standing together wearing headdresses], 14
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Four native women walking together], 15
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Four native women walking together], 16
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Native woman sitting on a stool next to a spinning wheel, making something], 17
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Man talking to an older native man], 18
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Three native women with red painted faces standing together], 19
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Close-up of a native woman standing], 20
  - Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea] [Items 1-6] Kodachrome Box number 1 [Items 7-11], circa 1963; 13 (Box 1590)
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Native people walking through tall grass], 1
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Palm trees], 2
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Palm trees], 3
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Native man and officer standing next to three other men], 4
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Native man wearing an elaborate headdress], 5
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Older native man talking with another man], 6
    - Beginning of Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake] Note: A listing of slides accompanies this slide presentation [: Lowell Thomas, Jr and girl looking at something], 7
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Dirt road, farmhouse], 8
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Men sitting outside and talking], 9
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Close-up of a man's face], 10
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Two men talking to each other on baseball field], 11
  - Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake] Note: A listing of slides accompanies this slide presentation, 1940; 14 (Box 1590)
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: A dog kennel], 1
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Two men talking together, smoking cigarettes], 2
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Lowell Thomas, Jr. on diving board], 3
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Chariot race], 4
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Man on construction vehicle holding golf clubs], 5
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Group of people standing outside of a building], 6
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Yoked cows], 7
  - Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake] Note: A listing of slides accompanies this slide presentation, 1940; 15 (Box 1590)
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Reflection of trees in a pond], 1
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Three men talking together on baseball field, Lowell Thomas at right ], 2
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: A white house], 3
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: A white house], 4
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Lowell Thomas talking to two other men], 5
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Sheep in a field], 6
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Sheep in a field], 7
  - Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake] Note: A listing of slides accompanies this slide presentation, 1940; 16 (Box 1590)
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: House], 1
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Lake?], 2
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Close-up of a man], 3
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Side of house, lake], 4
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: People swimming in lake, others having a picnic on the grass], 5
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Grass and cherry trees], 6
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Field, mountains in the distance], 7
  - Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake] Note: A listing of slides accompanies this slide presentation, 1940; 17 (Box 1590)
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: People mounted on houses, Lowell Thomas riding horse], 1
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Two men talking together on baseball field], 2
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Frances Ryan Thomas holding a dog], 3
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Two men looking at house], 4
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Inside of a house], 5
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Horses in corale, man standing by gate], 6
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: White house], 7
  - Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake] Note: A listing of slides accompanies this slide presentation, 1940; 18 (Box 1590)
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Lowell Thomas talking to man on a baseball field], 1
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Sign in front of house that says "Quaker Lake"], 2
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Lowell Thomas talking with a group of men], 3
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Man rowing a little boat], 4
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Lowell Thomas with a group of people talking], 5
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: A woman sitting between two men on a bench], 6
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Group of people outside], 7
  - Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake] Note: A listing of slides accompanies this slide presentation, 1940; 19 (Box 1590)
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Sunset behind house on a hill], 1
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Two horses on dirt road], 2
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Two horses pulling a plow], 3
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Man and a woman talking together], 4
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Fish laid out on white sheet], 5
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Man leaning against fence post], 6
  - Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake] Note: A listing of slides accompanies this slide presentation, 1940; 20 (Box 1590)
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas, Jr. in uniform sitting with Frances Ryan Thomas], 1
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Man leaning head out of window], 2
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Little girl with swimming cap on standing between two men], 3
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Lowell Thomas, Jr. diving into pool], 4
    - [Kodachrome box number 1 [Quaker Lake]: Baby sitting in front of dog outside], 5
  Box 1591
- 35 millimeter slides, 2.1.5.1
  - Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran], circa 1969; 1 (Box 1591)
    - Beginning of Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran] [: Three men talking together], 1
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Group of people sitting on ground, Lowell Thomas at right], 2
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: People riding by on horses], 3
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Men standing in a field], 4
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Man walking on mountaintop], 5
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Group of men on mountainside, some with guns on their backs], 6
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Group of men together with a cow], 7
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Trees], 8
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Vehicle driving on a dirt road, mountains ahead], 9
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Mountain goats], 10
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Man walking on a dirt road, mountains ahead], 11
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Man riding horse on dirt road, mountains ahead], 12
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Men riding horses on dirt road, mountains at the side], 13
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Mountain goats], 14
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Mountain goats], 15
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Men riding horses in a field], 16
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Men riding horses on dirt road, mountains ahead of them], 17
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Mountain goats], 18
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Mountain goats], 19
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Group of men on mountainside], 20
  - Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran], circa 1969; 2 (Box 1591)
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Mountain goats], 1
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Mountain goats], 2
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Mountain goats], 3
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Three men talking together], 4
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Building ahead (Mosque?)], 5
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Side of a stone building], 6
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: A throne], 7
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Portrait of a king?], 8
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: A throne], 9
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Man standing on steps], 10
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: A fancy couch], 11
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Portrait of a king?], 12
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: People working by a creek], 13
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Group of men standing on steps], 14
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Mountains], 15
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Men putting on a performance], 16
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Inside of a factory?], 17
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: People pouring contents into a bin], 18
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Inside of a factory? [looms making cloth (?)]], 19
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Men sitting on the ground, working], 20
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Man holding piece of metalwork], 21
  - Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran], circa 1969; 3 (Box 1591)
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Group of people in suits walking out of building], 1
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Group of people in suits and uniform, walking], 2
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: People together in bathing suits], 3
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Man walking by a high wall], 4
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Close-up of a woman's face], 5
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Close-up of a woman's face], 6
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Grand stone building with pillars], 7
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Man helping a woman up on a ledge], 8
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Woman standing in front of view of a city], 9
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Two women in bathing suits, smiling], 10
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: City square], 11
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Grand stone building with pillars], 12
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Man diving into a pool], 13
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: People climbing steps to diving board], 14
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Inside of a room wit ha fireplace and a chandelier], 15
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Top of a high ceiling], 16
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Man diving into pool], 17
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Tile work [Mosaic]], 18
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Hanging rug], 19
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Chandeliers], 20
  - Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran], circa 1969; 4 (Box 1591)
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Painting], 1
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Tilework], 2
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]:A room with a chandelier and a fireplace ], 3
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: A painted wall [fresco/ mural]], 4
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: A desk], 5
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Painting (embroidery?)], 6
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: A painted wall [fresco/ mural]], 7
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Chandelier], 8
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: A painted wall [fresco/ mural]], 9
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: A painted wall], 10
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: A painted wall], 11
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Painting (embroidery?)], 12
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Flower garden], 13
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Tilework], 14
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Flowers], 15
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Horses near a stone wall], 16
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Man taking photos outside], 17
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Fountain and a garden], 18
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Flower garden], 19
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Men working by a creek], 20
  - Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran], circa 1969; 5 (Box 1591)
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Flowers in pot], 1
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Gardens in front of pool], 2
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Flower garden in front of building], 3
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Barren land], 4
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Flowers in front of domed building], 5
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Large building], 6
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Large room with chandelier], 7
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Fountain], 8
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Artwork on wall], 9
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Carved [tiled (?)] entrance to building], 10
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Large room with chandelier], 11
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Fountain], 12
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Men with donkeys, 13
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Carved [tiled (?)] entrance], 14
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Food laid out on table], 15
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: People standing with horse], 16
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Horse carrying supplies], 17
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Horses carrying supplies], 18
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Man looking at tilework], 19
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: People working in a factory?], 20
  - Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran], circa 1969; 6 (Box 1591)
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: People walking outside of large building], 1
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Group of people standing on a roof, other people below standing outside], 2
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Mountains], 3
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Flower garden, park], 4
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Group of men standing together, mountains in background], 5
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Group of men talking], 6
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Large white building, gardens in back of it], 7
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Large swimming pool], 8
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Men gathered around a table laiden with food], 9
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: White [Tiled/ patterend] domed building], 10
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Construction on a building], 11
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: White domed [Tiled/ patterend] building], 12
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Group of men gathered together], 13
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Two men standing in front of swimming pool], 14
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Men mounted on horses], 15
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Group of men together, holding sticks], 16
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Group of men and boys holding sticks], 17
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Group of men standing at side of road, parked car], 18
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Men standing by a parked car], 19
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Boy riding a horse], 20
  - Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran], circa 1969; 7 (Box 1591)
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Men standing by a parked car], 1
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: (blurry photo)], 2
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Man crouched, taking a picture], 3
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: A galloping horse], 4
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Some men standing out in field, talking], 5
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Boys standing by donkeys], 6
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Two men standing and talking outside, city view], 7
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Oxen pulling a man], 8
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Dirt road, mountains ahead], 9
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Men mounted on horses, mountains in background], 10
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Men riding horses, mountain ahead], 11
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Men standing outside with cattle], 12
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Men riding horses on rocky terrain], 13
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Men standing by a parked car], 14
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Men riding horses], 15
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Men riding horses, mountain ahead], 16
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Men riding horses], 17
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Planes lined up], 18
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: Back of a pilot's head, flying a plane], 19
    - [Kodachrome box number 2 [Iran]: View of mountain from an airplane], 20
  - Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans], circa 1963; 8 (Box 1591)
    - Beginning of Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans] [: Lowell Thomas talking with a man, mountains in background], 1
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Lowell Thomas talking with a man, mountains in background], 2
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Lowell Thomas standing outside], 3
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Lowell Thomas talking with a man, mountains in background], 4
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Lowell Thomas talking with a group of men outside of a building], 5
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Lowell Thomas talking with a group of men outside of a building, pointing at a map], 6
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Lowell Thomas talking with a group of men outside of a building, LT reading from a book], 7
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Lowell Thomas talking with a man outside of a building], 8
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Lowell Thomas talking with a man outside of a building], 9
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Lowell Thomas standing behind a group of children], 10